{
    "id": "a2c2f59952364266b5f3289ebdbc9a06",
    "title": "All And Every Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………………………. child needs love.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "Every"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "26c85983e2fb480ab670afaa43a31e2a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have written to ……………………………… my friends.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dd70f5faa22246f585428ce543938bb7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have written to ……………………………… friend I have.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "25407623bab8456dbb0d2165b5ced6c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "My family …………………………….. work in education.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d8552ee5190444509f06d9d3959ccdc4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Not …………………………….. birds can sing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "92eb249d2883429587a5cfc613a1fd0e"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… person made his or her own travel arrangements.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Every",
                "All"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3226d59da8e242e0969b1b907aa1191c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I see her ………………………….. few days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "every",
                "all"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "46bc909a96364a4f99598cc002792f2b"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a meeting ……………………………… six weeks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "every",
                "all"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "78bad623e31d435abe39e976a141649c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have cleaned ……………………………. the rooms except the bathroom.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4b6a1f8c5c284c65ba746da1fe73dadf"
        },
        {
            "question": "You don’t see tigers ……………………………… day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a30c20f265a74a668cc50b23230620a9"
        }
    ]
}